<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Andrea Mauri</title>
    <link>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Andrea Mauri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Andrea Mauri</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.andreamauri.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at Rotterdam Knowledge Lab of Urban Big Data</title>
      <link>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/2019rotterdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/2019rotterdam/</guid>
      <description>On the 10th of October I gave a presentation for the Rotterdam Knowledge Lab of Urban Big Data on my work where I explored if and how new sources from the internet could complement conventional sources to study NEETs.
My research focuses on user-generated content posted to the dedicated r/NEET group on the platform Reddit, which gathers about 4800 subscribers who self-identify as NEETs. I developed and implemented a new method to assess the behavioral patterns and main concerns of the NEETs that are present in this data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to WWW!</title>
      <link>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/www/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/www/</guid>
      <description>Form the 23th to the 28th of April I&amp;rsquo;ll be at the Web Conference (WWW) held in Lyon.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be presenting the demo Social Smart Meter: Identifying Energy Consumption Behavior in User-Generated Content, which aim to investigate to which extent social media can be used as complementary source of information about individual energy consumption behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to ISWC!</title>
      <link>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/iswc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.andreamauri.com/post/iswc/</guid>
      <description>Form the 20th to the 26th of October I&amp;rsquo;ll be at the International Semantic Web Conference held in Vienna.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be presenting the demo Stressless RSP Benchmarking with RSPLab, which will show how RSPLab enables design of experiments using a programmatic interface that allows deploying the environment, running experiments, measuring the performance, visualizing the results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>